Margaret Bourke-White Papers
Margaret Bourke-White Papers
- Photographs, professional
  - Independent jobs
    - Journeyman (Caldwell play) [JOU], interpositives 10778-10890 (Box 366)
    - Journeyman (Caldwell play) [JOU], interpositives 10891-10959 (Box 367)
    - Katz, E., estate, Gates Mills [KGM], 1928 (Box 162, Folder 11-12)
    - Katz, E., estate, Gates Mills [KGM], interpositives 10960-10973 (Box 367)
    - Kaufman, Mrs. [KFN], interpositives 10974-10987 (Box 367)
    - Keenan, Michael [KEE], interpositives 10988 (Box 367)
    - Keller, Mr. K.T. [KEL], interpositives 10989-10991 (Box 367)
    - Kinney & Brown [KIN], interpositives 10992-10995 (Box 368)
    - Kirtland Country Club [KCC], interpositives 10996-11001 (Box 367)
    - Knowlton, Don, daughter [KNO], interpositives 11002-11006 (Box 368)
    - Kreyemborg, Arthur and Mrs. [KYB], interpositives 11007-11008 (Box 368)
    - Kroger Bakery [KRO], interpositives 11009-11013 (Box 368)
    - Kroger Grocery Warehouse [KGW], interpositives 11014-11027 (Box 367)
    - Kudner Agency [KUD], 1935; Buick (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Kudner Agency [KUD], 1935; Buick; Arthur-Kudner Inc. and Arthur Kudner (Box 163, Folder 1-11)
    - Kudner Agency [KUD], 1935-1936; Arthur-Kudner Inc. and Arthur Kudner (Box 164, Folder 1-8)
    - Kudner Agency [KUD], interpositives 11028-11205 (Box 367)
    - Kuh, Frederick [KUH], 1932 (Box 164, Folder 8-10)
    - Kuh, Renata [KUH] (Box 164, Folder 10-11)
    - Kuh, Frederick/Renata [KUH], interpositives 11206-11228 (Box 368)
    - Kulas and secretary [KAS], interpositives 11229-11246 (Box 367)
    - Ladies' Home Journal [LHJ], 1933 (Box 164, Folder 11-12)
    - Ladies' Home Journal [LHJ], 1933 (Box 165, Folder 1-7)
    - La Salle [LAS] (Box 165, Folder 7-10)
    - La Salle [LAS], interpositives 11333-11362 (Box 368)
    - Lee, Carl R. [LEE], interpositives 11363; 11367-11368 (Box 368)
    - Letchworth Village [LET], 1932 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Letchworth Village [LET], 1932 (Box 167, Folder 1-4)
    - Letchworth Village [LET], interpositives 11393-11408; 11415-11441 (Box 368)
      LIT 11409 on same sheet as LET 11408; for LET 11391 see LEH 11388.
    - Limestone Clock [LSE], 1933 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Limestone Clock [LSE], interpositives 11446-11447 (Box 369)
    - Lincoln Electric [LCL], 1929 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Lincoln Electric [LCL], 1929 (Box 167, Folder 5-7)
    - Lincoln Electric [LCL], 1929 (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
    - Lincoln Electric [LCL], 1929 (Oversize 7, Folder 6)
    - Lincoln Electric [LCL], interpositives 11448-11468 (Box 368)
    - Litschutz family [LIT], interpositives 11409-11414, for LIT 11409 see LET 11409 (Box 368)
    - Louisville, Kentucky, flood story (Box 166, Folder 1-2)
    - Louisville, Kentucky, flood story (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Louisville, Kentucky, flood story (Oversize 7, Folder 7-8)
    - Dr. Hans Luther [LTR], See Germany: Dr. Hans Luther [LTR].
    - Lynn Bond Shoe Factory [LBS], 1929 (Box 167, Folder 7-10)
    - Lynn Bond Shoe Factory [LBS], interpositives 11493-11511 (Box 368)
    - Lyon Metal Products [LYO], interpositives 11481-11492 (Box 369)
    - Malamed's daughter [MMD], interpositives 11550-11555 (Box 371)
    - McCall's [MCL] (Box 167, Folder 10-11)
    - McCall's [MCL], interpositives 11512-11517 (Box 371)
    - Machine shop, A.L. Adams [MSA] (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Machine shop, A.L. Adams [MSA] (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Machine shop, A.L. Adams [MSA], interpositives 11518-11539 (Box 371)
    - Macy's Bureau of Standards / Chemistry lab [MAC] (Box 168, Folder 1-3)
    - Macy's Bureau of Standards / Chemistry lab [MAC], interpositives 11540-11549 (Box 369)
    - Martini Rossi [MTR], interpositives 11556-11634 (Box 372)
      See also Richardson [RIC].
    - Meldrum and Fewsmith (Chrysler gargoyles) [MAF], interpositives 11635-11661 (Box 369)
    - Mentor Harbor [MTH], interpositives 11662-11667 (Box 371)
    - Miller Industries [MRI], 1931 (Box 168, Folder 3-7)
    - Miller Industries [MRI], interpositives 11668-11675 (Box 371)
    - Munger, Jessie D., estate, Plainfield, NJ [MUN], 1927 (Box 168, Folder 7-8)
    - Munger, Jessie D., estate, Plainfield, NJ [MUN], 1927 (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
    - Munger, Jessie D., estate, Plainfield, NJ [MUN], interpositives 11676-11697 (Box 372)
    - Murals for the home [MRL], interpositives 11698-11706 (Box 371)
    - Murray Arthur [MAM] (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Murray Arthur [MAM], interpositives 11707-11710 (Box 369)
    - National Broadcasting Company (NBC) [NBC]
      - Mural (Box 166, Folder 2-5)
      - Mural (Box 168, Folder 8-9)
      - Mural, includes sending station in Bellmore, Long Island (Box 169, Folder 1-10)
      - Mural (Box 170, Folder 1-11)
      - Mural (Box 171, Folder 1-11)
      - Mural (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Studio Orchestra (Box 172, Folder 1-5)
      - Switches (Box 172, Folder 5-7)
      - Television (Box 172, Folder 7-9)
      - WAEF Broadcasting Tower, Bellmore, Long Island (Box 172, Folder 9-11)
      - WAEF Broadcasting Tower, Bellmore, Long Island (Box 173, Folder 1-7)
      - WAEF Broadcasting Tower, Bellmore, Long Island (Box 176, Folder 7)
      - WAEF Broadcasting Tower, Bellmore, Long Island (Oversize 7, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous [NBC] interpositives 11711-11739 (Box 375)
      - Miscellaneous [NBC] interpositives 11740-12013 (Box 376)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) [NEA]
      - NEA, 1934 (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Backstage (Box 174, Folder 6-11)
      - Boulder Dam, 1935 (Box 174, Folder 11-13)
      - Senator [William] Borah, 1934 (Box 174, Folder 13)
      - Senator [William] Borah, 1934 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - The Capitol, 1934 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Cleveland, Halle Bros. Department Store, 1934 (Box 175, Folder 1-1)
      - Dust storms, 1935 (Box 175, Folder 2-5)
      - Dust storms, 1935 (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
      - Flowers (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Washington, D.C (Box 175, Folder 6-9)
      - MGM, "The Flame Within", 1935 (Box 175, Folder 9-10)
      - New Department of Labor building, 1934 (Box 175, Folder 10-11)
      - Newport, [1934?] (Box 175, Folder 11)
      - Newport (Box 176, Folder 1-5)
      - Newport (Box 176, Folder 7-10)
      - Newport, 1934 (Oversize 7, Folder 8-9)
      - Olympics, 1936 (Box 176, Folder 5-7, 12)
      - Olympics, 1936 (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - President Roosevelt, 1934 (Box 176, Folder 10)
      - President Roosevelt, 1934 (Box 177, Folder 3-6)
      - President Roosevelt, 1934 (Oversize 7, Folder 9)
      - Washington, D.C.; Statue of Liberty (Box 177, Folder 6-12)
      - Wall Street [WST] (Box 178, Folder 1-1)
      - Wall Street [WST], interpositives 19775-19777 (Box 399)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 177, Folder 1-3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous [NEA] interpositives 12956-13239 (Box 377)
      - Miscellaneous [NEA] interpositives 13240-13529 (Box 378)
      - Miscellaneous [NEA] interpositives 13530-13624 (Box 379)
    - Necktie District (Box 178, Folder 2-3)
    - New Theatre Group [NTG], interpositives 13631-13640 (Box 380)
    - New York Central [NYC], 1937 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - New York Central [NYC], interpositives 13641-13646 (Box 380)
    - New York City (Box 178, Folder 5-6)
    - New York Journal [NYJ], interpositives 13668-13673 (Box 380)
    - New York skyline [NYS], interpositives 13674-13676 (Box 380)
    - New York street scenes [NSS], interpositives 13647-13667 (Box 379)
      See also Erwin Wasey and Company: Street scenes New York which may be the same job.
    - New York Tuberculosis Society [NYT], 1934 (Box 178, Folder 6-8)
    - New York Tuberculosis Society [NYT], interpositives 13677-13683 (Box 380)
    - Newell, John Jr., estate [NJJ], 1928 (Box 178, Folder 3-4)
    - Newell, John Jr., estate [NJJ], interpositives 13625-13630 (Box 379)
    - Niagara Falls [NGF], interpositives 13684-13693 (Box 379)
    - (Blackman) Niagara Hudson steam turbine [NHS] (Box 178, Folder 8-11)
    - (Blackman) Niagara Hudson steam turbine [NHS], interpositives 13694-13701 (Box 379)
    - Niagara Hudson Power Company [NHP], interpositives 13702-13725 (Box 379)
    - Northrup Memorial Camp [NMC], 1940 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Northrup Memorial Camp [NMC], 1940 (Box 179, Folder 1-4)
    - Northrup Memorial Camp [NMC], interpositives 13726-13791 (Box 379)
    - Orchid Conservatory [OCY], 1929 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Orchid Conservatory [OCY], interpositives 13792-13808 (Box 380)
    - Ore piles [OPS], interpositives 13809-13812 (Box 380)
    - Ornstein, Mrs. [ORN], interpositives 13813-13848 (Box 380)
    - Otis Steel Mill, Cleveland, Ohio [OSM], 1929 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Otis Steel Mill, Cleveland, Ohio [OSM], 1929 (Box 179, Folder 5-11)
    - Otis Steel Mill, Cleveland, Ohio [OSM], 1929 (Oversize 7, Folder 9)
    - Otis Steel Mill, Cleveland, Ohio [OSM], 1929 (Oversize 8, Folder 1-3)
    - Otis Steel Mill, Cleveland, Ohio [OSM], interpositives 13849-13918 (Box 380)
    - Oxford Paper Company [OPC], 1932 (Box 179, Folder 11-13)
    - Oxford Paper Company [OPC], 1932 (Box 180, Folder 1-5)
    - Oxford Paper Company [OPC], interpositives 13919-13962 (Box 380)
    - Pan American Airways (Pan Am) [PAA]
      - Buenos Aires, [1936] (Box 181, Folder 10-11)
      - Coffee plantation, 1936 (Box 176, Folder 11-12)
      - Coffee plantation, 1936 (Box 181, Folder 11-13)
      - Coffee plantation, 1936 (Box 182, Folder 1-4)
      - Coffee plantation, 1936 (Oversize 8, Folder 4)
      - Rio de Janeiro, 1936 (Box 180, Folder 10-12)
      - Rio de Janeiro, 1936 (Box 181, Folder 1-10)
      - Sikorsky S-42, 1934 (Box 180, Folder 5-10)
      - Miscellaneous [PAA] interpositives 13963-14060 (Box 380)
      - Miscellaneous [PAA] interpositives 14061-14330 (Box 381)
      - Miscellaneous [PAA] interpositives 14331-14471 (Box 382)
    - SS Paris, French Line [PSS] (Box 182, Folder 4-5)
    - SS Paris, French Line [PSS], interpositives 14472-14473 (Box 383)
    - Pepper Pike Country Club [PPC], interpositives 14480-14496 (Box 383)
    - Perfection stove, McCann Co. [PSM], interpositives 14497-14500 (Box 383)
    - Perkins Institute [PKI], 1932 (Box 182, Folder 5-7)
    - Perkins Institute [PKI], interpositives 14524-14527 (Box 383)
    - Pierce Arrow [PAW] (Box 182, Folder 7-10)
    - Pierce Arrow [PAW], interpositives 14529; 14535-14547 (Box 382)
    - Pitkin and Mott [PKM], interpositives 14549-14560 (Box 383)
    - Polio [POL] (Box 182, Folder 10-12)
    - Polio [POL], interpositives 14585-14596 (Box 383)
    - Portland Cement Company [PCC], interpositives 14597-14604 (Box 383)
      See also Fortune: Lehigh Portland Cement above, which may be the same company.
    - Post Office [POE], interpositives 14605-14608 (Box 383)
    - Prentis, Mrs. F.F., estate [PRE], 1928 (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Prentis, Mrs. F.F., estate [PRE], 1928 (Box 183, Folder 1-3)
    - Prentis, Mrs. F.F., estate [PRE], interpositives 14609-14679 (Box 383)
    - Price Brothers Paper, Ltd. [PBS], 1932 (Box 183, Folder 3-11)
    - Price Brothers Paper, Ltd. [PBS], 1932 (Box 184, Folder 2-12)
    - Price Brothers Paper, Ltd. [PBS], 1932 (Box 185, Folder 1-3)
    - Price Brothers Paper, Ltd. [PBS], 1932 (Oversize 8, Folder 5)
    - Price Brothers Paper, Ltd. [PBS], interpositives 14680-14695; 14701-14879 (Box 382)
    - Public Square [PUB], interpositives 14880-14894 (Box 383)
    - Radio City [RAD], 1933 (Box 185, Folder 3-5)
    - Radio City [RAD], interpositives 14895-14944, missing 14913 (Box 383)
    - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) [RCA], 1931 (Box 185, Folder 5-8)
    - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) [RCA], interpositives 14945-15023 (Box 384)
    - Redbook [RBK], 1935; St. Louis (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Redbook [RBK], interpositives 15029-15050 (Box 383)
    - Redbook [RBK], interpositives 15051-15071 (Box 384)
    - Republic Steel Corporation [RIS] (Box 185, Folder 10-12)
    - Republic Steel Corporation [RIS] (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
    - Republic Steel Corporation [RIS], interpositives 15072-15116 (Box 384)
    - Richardson [RIC], 1935; Martini & Rossi (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - Richardson [RIC], interpositives 15117-15122 (Box 384)
    - Rorimer-Brooks Powers House [RBP], interpositives 15123-15125 (Box 384)
    - Rosenbaum Grain [RGC], 1931 (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - Rosenbaum Grain [RGC], 1931 (Box 186, Folder 1-5)
    - Rosenbaum Grain [RGC], 1931 (Oversize 8, Folder 5)
    - Rosenbaum Grain [RGC], interpositives 15126-15177 (Box 384)
    - Ross, Walter [ROS], interpositives 15178-15191 (Box 384)
    - Royal Typewriter [ROY] (Box 186, Folder 5-10)
    - Royal Typewriter [ROY], interpositives 15192-15228 (Box 384)
    - Rumford Paper Co. [RPM] (Box 186, Folder 10-11)
    - Rumford Paper Co. [RPM] (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Rumford Paper Co. [RPM], interpositives 15229-15235 (Box 384)
    - Russell, Albert W., estate [RAW] (Box 187, Folder 1-3)
    - Russell, Albert W., estate [RAW], interpositives 15236-15287 (Box 383)
    - Russell Birdsall Ward, 1930 (Box 187, Folder 3-7)
    - St. Louis (not Redbook) [STL], interpositives 15390-15403 (Box 392)
    - Saw blades [SBL] (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Scheider [SCH], interpositives 15404-15669 (Box 390)
    - Scheider [SCH], interpositives 15670-15693 (Box 391)
    - Scripps-Howard [SCR], 1934-1935; includes canoeist (Box 187, Folder 8-12)
    - Scripps-Howard [SCR], 1934-1935 (Box 188, Folder 1-4)
    - Seagrams Distillery [SEA] (Box 188, Folder 4-7)
    - Seagrams Distillery [SEA], interpositives 15694-15732 (Box 391)
    - Sears Roebuck [SSR] (Box 188, Folder 7-9)
    - Sears Roebuck [SSR], interpositives 15733-15761 (Box 392)
    - Seid, Herman [SEI], 1933 (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Seid, Herman [SEI], interpositives 15762-15765 (Box 391)
    - Selby Shoes [SSC], 1934 (Box 188, Folder 9-11)
    - Selby Shoes [SSC], 1934 (Box 189, Folder 1-4)
    - Selby Shoes [SSC], interpositives 15766-15800 (Box 391)
    - Selby Shoes [SSC], interpositives 15801-15846 (Box 392)
    - Seminary of Our Lady of the Lake [SLL], interpositives 15855-15862 (Box 391)
    - Shadow Lane [SDL] (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Shadow Lane [SDL], interpositives 15855-15858 (Box 391)
    - Shaker Heights Village [SHS] (Box 189, Folder 4-5)
    - Shaker Heights Village [SHS], interpositives 15859-15871 (Box 391)
    - Sheridan, Frank [SDN] (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Sheridan, Frank [SDN], interpositives 15872-15877 (Box 391)
    - Sherwin, John, estate [SWN], 1927 (Box 189, Folder 5-7)
    - Sherwin, John, estate [SWN], interpositives 15878-15924 (Box 392)
    - Shook, Virginia [SHO], 1935 (Box 189, Folder 7-8)
    - Shook, Virginia [SHO], interpositives 15925-15936 (Box 391)
    - Sindelar, J.F. [SIN], interpositives 15937-15941; 15943 (Box 391)
    - Smith, Leonard Jr. [SMI], interpositives 15943-15944 (Box 391)
    - Sokolof, Nikolai [SOK], interpositives 15945-15951 (Box 391)
    - South Bend Fishing Tackle Co. (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Standard Oil Company [SOC], 1937 (Box 189, Folder 8-10)
    - Standard Oil Company [SOC], interpositives 16022-16079 (Box 391)
    - Steer, prize [STR], interpositives 16080-16081 (Box 392)
    - Sullivan, Dr. Henry Stack [SUL], 1932 (Box 189, Folder 10-11)
    - Sullivan, Dr. Henry Stack [SUL], interpositives 16083-16086 (Box 392)
    - Swift & Company, Redbook [SWI], 1932 (Box 189, Folder 11)
      See also Fortune: Swift & Co..
    - Swift & Company, Redbook [SWI], interpositives 16087-16112 (Box 392)
    - Symphonie Powder, L.S. Ayres and Son [SPA] (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Symphonie Powder, L.S. Ayres and Son [SPA], interpositives 16113-16125 (Box 391)
    - Taggard, Miss [TAG], 1934 (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
    - Taggard, Miss [TAG], interpositives 16126-16131 (Box 392)
    - Taylor Whiskey [TWC] (Box 190, Folder 2-3)
    - Taylor Whiskey [TWC], interpositives 16132-16143 (Box 397)
    - Terminal Tower, Cleveland [TTC] (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Terminal Tower, Cleveland [TTC] (Box 190, Folder 3-12)
    - Terminal Tower, Cleveland [TTC] (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
    - Terminal Tower, Cleveland [TTC] (Oversize 8, Folder 6)
    - Terminal Tower, Cleveland [TTC], interpositives 16144-16355 (Box 393)
    - Theatre Guild [THG] (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Theatre Guild [THG] (Box 191, Folder 1-2)
    - Theatre Guild [THG], interpositives 16368-16391 (Box 392)
    - Theatre Union, 1935; "The Black Pit" (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, Edgar [THE], interpositives 16392-16396 (Box 392)
    - [J. Walter] Thompson Company [TJW], 1934 (Box 191, Folder 3-7)
    - [J. Walter] Thompson Company [TJW], interpositives 16411-16464 (Box 392)
    - Thompson Koch Company [TKC] (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Thompson Koch Company [TKC], interpositives 16397-16410 (Box 392)
    - Thompson, Stouder, estate [TNS], 1928 (Box 191, Folder 2-3)
    - Thompson, Stouder, estate [TNS], interpositives 16465-16491 (Box 392)
    - Trade Winds [TWS] (Box 191, Folder 7-8)
    - Trade Winds [TWS], interpositives 16494-16499 (Box 397)
    - TWA [Trans World Airlines] [TWA]
      - Acoma Village (Box 191, Folder 8-11)
      - Acoma Village (Box 192, Folder 1-2)
      - Boulder Dam (Box 192, Folder 2-5)
      - Enchanted Mesa, Inscription Rock, San Francisco (Box 192, Folder 5-9)
      - Grand Canyon (Box 192, Folder 9-11)
      - Grand Canyon (Box 193, Folder 1-4)
      - Grand Coulee Dam [also LIFE Job #673-A, 673-B, 673-E] (Box 193, Folder 4-5)
      - Hangars and airports (Box 193, Folder 5-7)
      - Officials (Box 193, Folder 7-10)
      - Officials (Box 194, Folder 1-3)
      - Passengers in plane (Box 194, Folder 3-10)
      - Planes in flight (Box 194, Folder 10-11)
      - Planes in flight (Box 195, Folder 1-11)
      - Planes in flight (Box 196, Folder 1-10)
      - Plant and maintenance (Box 196, Folder 10-12)
      - Plant and maintenance (Box 197, Folder 1)
      - Pilots (Box 197, Folder 1-5)
      - [Miscellaneous] (Box 197, Folder 5-6)
      - Sierra Madre Mountains, craters, Arrowhead Lake (Box 197, Folder 7-11)
      - Sierra Madre Mountains, craters, Arrowhead Lake (Box 215, Folder 6-7)
      - Sierra Madre Mountains, craters, Arrowhead Lake (Oversize 7, Folder 4)
      - Sierra Madre Mountains, craters, Arrowhead Lake (Oversize 9, Folder 4-5)
      - Miscellaneous [TWA] interpositives 16499-16530 (Box 393)
      - Miscellaneous [TWA] interpositives 16531-16860, missing 16651, 16552, 16740 (Box 394)
      - Miscellaneous [TWA] interpositives 16861-17169 (Box 395)
      - Miscellaneous [TWA] interpositives 17170-17484 (Box 396)
      - Miscellaneous [TWA] interpositives 17485-17658 (Box 397)
    - Tuberculosis Association [TBA], interpositives 17659-17660 (Box 392)
    - Tulips, Grand Central Palace [TUL], 1934 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Tulips, Grand Central Palace, interpositives 17661-17688 (Box 393)
    - Turtles on terrace [TOT], interpositives 17689-17690 (Box 393)
    - Underwood and Underwood [UAU], interpositives 17691 (Box 397)
    - Union Fork and Hoe [UFH] (Box 197, Folder 11-12)
    - Union Fork and Hoe [UFH] (Box 198, Folder 1-2)
    - Union Fork and Hoe [UFH], interpositives 17692-17782 (Box 397)
    - Union Trust Company [UTR], 1930 (Box 198, Folder 2-3)
    - Union Trust Company [UTR], interpositives 17783-17788 (Box 398)
    - Union Fruit Company [UNF] (Box 198, Folder 3-4)
    - Union Fruit Company [UNF], interpositives 17789-17791 (Box 397)
    - U.S. Rubber Products Incorporated [USR], 1935; includes Passaic factory (Box 198, Folder 4-11)
    - U.S. Rubber Products Incorporated [USR], interpositives 17792-17842 (Box 398)
    - University of Michigan, 1924 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Valiant, Margaret [VAL], 1933 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Valiant, Margaret [VAL], interpositives 17846-17847 (Box 398)
    - Van Blarcom, Conant, estate [VAN], 1927 (Box 199, Folder 1-2)
    - Van Blarcom, Conant, estate [VAN], interpositives 17849-17870 (Box 398)
    - Vassos, John [VAS], includes some with his dog (Box 199, Folder 2-3)
    - Vassos, John [VAS], interpositives 17871-17875 (Box 398)
    - Vassos, John, D.A. tooth powder [VAT], interpositives 17876-17879 (Box 398)
    - Vassos, John, dog [VDG], interpositives 17880-17890 (Box 398)
    - Vassos, John, and dog [VSD], interpositives 17891-17899 (Box 398)
    - Vassos, John, silverware [VSS], interpositives 17900-17904 (Box 398)
    - Violinist's hands [VTH], Herr Klaus Liepmann (Box 183, Folder 11-12)
    - Violinist's hands [VTH], Herr Klaus Liepmann (Box 199, Folder 3-4)
    - Violinist's hands [VTH], Herr Klaus Liepmann (Oversize 8, Folder 6)
    - Violinist's hands [VTH], interpositives 17905-17918 (Box 398)
    - Vogue [VUE], interpositives 17919-17923 (Box 398)
    - Warner and Swazey [WAS], interpositives 17924-17927 (Box 398)
    - Wellman Seaver Morgan [WEE], interpositives 17928-17942 (Box 398)
    - Wells, Sidney [WEL], interpositives 17943-17945 (Box 398)
    - West Point Textile [WES], 1936 (Box 199, Folder 4-6)
    - West Point Textile [WES], interpositives 17946-17964 (Box 398)
    - West Point Textile [WES], interpositives 17965-17998 (Box 399)
    - Westinghouse, Cleveland [WET] (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Westinghouse, Cleveland [WET], interpositives 17999-18004 (Box 399)
    - Wheat field [WHE], interpositives 18006 (Box 399)
    - White, Robert, portrait [WHI], interpositives 18007-18017 (Box 399)
    - Whithorne, Mr. [WHT], interpositives 18018-18025 (Box 399)
    - Willard Battery [WIL], interpositives 18026-18029 (Box 399)
    - Williams [WIM], interpositives 18039-18036 (Box 399)
    - Wilson Co. [WIS], interpositives 18037-18041 (Box 399)
    - Wolff, Sam [WOL] (Box 199, Folder 6-7)
    - Wolff, Sam [WOL], interpositives 18042-18043 (Box 399)
    - Woodstock, NY, waiter [WOO], interpositives 18044-18061 (Box 399)
    - W.O.R. [WOR], 1935 (Box 199, Folder 7-8)
    - W.O.R. [WOR], interpositives 18062-18106 (Box 399)
    - World's Fair [WRF], Chicago, 1933-1934 (Box 199, Folder 9-10)
    - World's Fair [WRF], Chicago interpositives 18107-18123 (Box 399)
    - World's Fair [WRF], New York, 1940 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - [World's Fair, New York] Soviet Pavilion D [SPD], interpositives 15952-16021 (Box 391)
    - Wrigley Company, William Wrigley, Jr. [WRI] (Box 199, Folder 10-12)
      See also Fortune: Wrigley above.
    - Wrigley Company, William Wrigley, Jr. [WRI] (Box 200, Folder 1-2)
    - Wrigley Company, William Wrigley, Jr. [WRI], interpositives 18124-18132 (Box 399)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph Jr., estate, [WUR], 1929 (Box 200, Folder 3-6)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph Jr., estate, [WUR], interpositives 18133-18147 (Box 399)
    - Young, John [YOO], interpositives 18148-18152 (Box 399)
  - LIFE magazine jobs
    Bourke-White was sent on numerous photographic assignments for LIFE magazine over the course of her career (the very first issue of the magazine bore one of her photographs on the cover). Groups of material in this subseries are arranged in order by LIFE job number, thus roughly chronologically. Assignments included companies/organizations (Grumman Aircraft, Strategic Air Command, American Jesuits), places (Mt. Wilson observatory, Jersey City, Wenner Gren Land, Syria, Russia, North Africa), individuals (James Farley, Cordell Hull), and topics (food, Hollywood sets, London blackout, America from a helicopter). Not all of Bourke-White's Life assignments are represented in the collection; for a complete list of Life jobs, compiled by staff, see under Biographical material above.
    - Senate [LIFE Job #43], 1937 (Box 200, Folder 7-11)
    - Senate [LIFE Job #43], 1937 (Box 201, Folder 1-3)
    - Bermuda Clipper [LIFE Job #92 and 418], 1937 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Skyport [LIFE Job #253], 1937 (Box 201, Folder 3-4)
    - Bellanca Factory, Wilmington [BEL] [LIFE Job #257] (Box 116, Folder 8-9)
    - Bellanca Factory, Wilmington [BEL] [LIFE Job #257], interpositives 4262-4284 (Box 343)
    - Grumman Aircraft [LIFE Job #332], 1937 (Box 201, Folder 4-6)